yvr.ca 2018-11-22

# Privacy | YVR

Vancouver Airport Authority is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals.

Click here to download our complete privacy policy.

### How Information is Collected and Used

The Authority collects personal information that is voluntarily provided by you when using certain portions of this website; such as 'contact us' and 'reservations'. This information is collected for the purpose in which it was given; respond to your inquiry, ship your product, or make your reservation. By providing us with your personal information, you consent to the use of your personal information in accordance with this privacy statement. The Authority will not disclose any personal information to any third party, except as required by law and as is necessary to fulfill your request.

### Cookies and Log Files

Cookies are data files sent to your browser and stored on your hard-drive when you visit certain websites. This enables a company to track your visit to the site. The Authority uses per-session cookies. Per-session cookies track your usage on our website during the current visit only and are deleted once you exit the site. The Authority has log files, which records the IP address of your computer. The Authority uses log files to track the number of hits to its website.

If you would like to deactivate cookies, please see below for links that provide detailed information for cookie deactivation in commonly used browsers:

### Storage of and Access to Personal Information

Personal information submitted through 'contact us' is retained for the period of time it takes to respond to you. Personal information submitted through 'e-commerce' is kept on a database. Upon request, the Authority will provide you with access to any personal information it has collected through its website. Requests for access to personal information should be sent via email through the 'contact us' portion of the website. Personal information will be updated or deleted at your request.

### Security

The Authority does not represent, warrant or guarantee that personal information is protected from loss or misuse, including misuse of third parties, nor the accuracy of the information provided. The Authority has taken security measures with respect to the storage of personal information in the attempt to maintain the safety of such information.

### Links

This website contains links to third party sites. The Authority is not responsible for the collection of personal information nor the privacy of such information on third party sites.

If you have any questions or concerns with respect to this privacy statement, please send an email through Contact Us. Or download our complete privacy policy here.

The Authority reserves the right to change this privacy statement at any time. Such changes will be posted on this page and in compliance with applicable federal privacy laws.
